Childe Leng,
تشايلد لينغ ،
looking at your face, you don't change your color and your heart doesn't beat,
بالنظر إلى وجهك ، لا تغير لونك ولا ينبض قلبك ،
You won.
لقد فزت.
To you for being a hero.
لك لكونك بطلا.
After you,
بعدك،
Childe Zhou.
تشيلدي تشو.
You can treat me first.
يمكنك معاملتي أولا.
That's all.
هذا كل شئ.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Are they going to start?
هل سيبدأون؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
The two contestants are ready for the final battle.
المتسابقان جاهزان للمعركة النهائية.
At the same time, they ate the red pepper
في نفس الوقت أكلوا الفلفل الأحمر
symbolizing determination.
يرمز إلى العزيمة.
After eating Rejuvenation Red Pepper,
بعد تناول الفلفل الأحمر لتجديد شباب البشرة ،
they are about to face the final test.
هم على وشك مواجهة الاختبار النهائي.
Ouch! Death-taking Soul-taking Pot?
أوتش!  القدر القاتل للروح؟
Now let's hold our breath
الآن دعونا نحبس أنفاسنا
and concentrate on the final battle.
والتركيز على المعركة النهائية.
It's not spicy at all.
إنه ليس حارًا على الإطلاق.
Please.
لو سمحت.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Let's go together.
لنذهب معا.
Let's do it first.
لنفعل ذلك أولاً.
I won.
انا ربحت.
There's only one bowl of instant noodles left.
لم يتبق سوى وعاء واحد من المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
I'm not hungry.
انا لست جائع.
I want to lose weight.
أريد أن أخسر وزن.
When you become a superstar in the future,
عندما تصبح نجما في المستقبل ،
you should eat it.
يجب أن تأكله.
How about we eat half for each of us?
ماذا لو نأكل نصف لكل واحد منا؟
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay.
تمام.
Did you burn your stomach?
هل حرقت معدتك؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
No way.
مستحيل.
It'll leave a scar.
ستترك ندبة.
It's okay.
حسنا.
I'm a master.
انا سيد.
It's normal to have a scar,
من الطبيعي أن يكون لديك ندبة ،
but when I see the scar on your stomach in the future,
لكن عندما أرى الندبة على معدتك في المستقبل ،
I knew it was you.
كنت أعلم أنه أنت.
Don't make so much noise.
لا تصدر الكثير من الضوضاء.
There's only one seat in here.
هناك مقعد واحد فقط هنا.
Line up.
اصطفوا.
Line up at the back.
اصطف في الخلف.
This is such a stupid toilet.
هذا هو مثل هذا المرحاض الغبي.
Why is there no toilet paper?
لماذا لا يوجد ورق تواليت؟
Get out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
How could he cut in line?
كيف يمكنه قطع الخط؟
Line up.
اصطفوا.
I can't take it.
لا أستطيع أخذها.
Toilet paper.
ورق التواليت.
I forgot to mention,
نسيت أن أذكر،
toilet paper
ورق التواليت
There's also a charge.
هناك أيضًا رسوم.
What?
ماذا؟
How much
كم الثمن
is it?
فعلا؟
10 taels?
10 تايل؟
Why don't you just rob the bank?
لماذا لا تسرق البنك فقط؟
It's illegal to rob a bank.
من غير القانوني سرقة بنك.
Besides,
بجانب،
this business sells toilet paper,
يبيع هذا العمل ورق التواليت ،
It's about your love and my wish.
إنه يتعلق بحبك وأمنيتي.
You don't have to.
لا داعي لذلك.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Here,
هنا،
Toilet paper.
ورق التواليت.
Toilet paper. Hurry up.
ورق التواليت.  عجلوا.
Line up.
اصطفوا.
Master,
يتقن،
wait in line too.
انتظر في الطابور أيضا.
Treasure Pavilion was stolen.
سرقت كنز بافيليون.
What did you lose?
ماذا خسرت؟
I've sent someone to check it.
لقد أرسلت شخصًا ما للتحقق من ذلك.
I lost a lot of things.
لقد فقدت الكثير من الأشياء.
What?
ماذا؟
Mu Feng,
مو فنغ ،
stop.
قف.
Sister, what are you talking about?
أخت ، ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Tomorrow is Mu Yun's death anniversary.
غدا ذكرى وفاة مو يون.
Vengeance has no time to be avenged.
ليس لدى الانتقام وقت للانتقام.
Besides,
بجانب،
that's enough.
هذا يكفي.
Other than telling the truth to our brothers,
بخلاف قول الحق لإخواننا ،
what else can you do?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل أيضا؟
All of this happened because of those people outside.
كل هذا حدث بسبب هؤلاء الناس في الخارج.
Including you.
بما فيهم أنت.
That's what you think?
هذا ما تظنه؟
I'm tired.
أنا مجهد.
Mu Feng,
مو فنغ ،
get out.
اخرج.
Okay,
تمام،
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
However,
لكن،
I hope you won't make mistakes again and again.
آمل ألا ترتكب أخطاء مرارًا وتكرارًا.
In this way, Mu Yun
بهذه الطريقة ، مو يون
can rest in peace in the grave
يمكن أن يرقد بسلام في القبر
Sis,
الاخت ،
Have you thought it through?
هل فكرت فيه؟
Don't blame me.
لا تلومني.
Don't blame
لا تلوم
my silly brother,
أخي السخيف
You're right. It's all Hunian's fault.
أنت على حق.  هذا كله خطأ هونيان.
I didn't take good care of your brother.
لم أعتني بأخيك جيدًا.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Sis,
الاخت ،
Don't die.
لا تموت.
Don't die, okay?
لا تموت ، حسناً؟
Sister.
أخت.
After nearly a month of fierce competition,
بعد قرابة شهر من المنافسة الشرسة ،
this Sword Worship Conference has finally come to an end.
لقد انتهى مؤتمر عبادة السيف هذا أخيرًا.
Next,
التالي،
let me introduce you.
دعني أقدمك.
The rules of the third round,
قواعد الجولة الثالثة ،
the rules of this round are very simple,
قواعد هذه الجولة بسيطة للغاية ،
Similar,
مماثل،
Hide and seek,
الغميضة،
I'll be the pursuer.
سأكون المطارد.
As escapees,
هاربين ،
isn't it easy?
أليس هذا سهلا؟
As a genius,
عبقري ،
I have given this project
لقد قدمت هذا المشروع
a very nice name.
اسم جميل جدا.
Run away, bro.
اهرب يا أخي.
Run, bro.
تشغيل ، إخوانه.
Now I announce,
الآن أعلن ،
the competition begins.
تبدأ المنافسة.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Two.
اثنين.
One.
واحد.
Come on!
هيا!
The sword
السيف
is on fire.
انه يحترق.